(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) we spent the last few years looking for
the most perfect beauty products and we found
some really great stuff.
and a lot of them we still love.
but somehow there would always be a but.
I love this formula but the colors just
aren't right.
I love what this product does but it's
just a little too expensive.
I love this packaging but the branding isn't
me.
we looked everywhere.
no brand, no manufacturer, no price point was
overlooked.
and then we asked ourselves will we ever
find one brand that has everything we love
about makeup?
one brand that just gets us completely.
22 formulas, 350 color samples later, we think
we've managed to create the best lip ever.
meet Sunny's Face.
Sunny's Face is beauty inspired by our girl
crushes.
what makes a girl crush is a girl
that's so confident in her own skin.
you can't quite put your finger on it
but you're like I really like you, like
I want to be your friend, I want
to be you.
you know those women that just have something
about them where it looks so natural, approachable,
pretty but effortless.
it's the perfect in-between.
girl crush beauty isn't about transforming your face.
it's not about wearing a mask and wearing
all this contour that you don't even look
like yourself.
and it's also not the no makeup makeup
look.
no, let's be real.
we still love makeup.
we love makeup and we want to show
it.
really natural but dewy skin, like really really
healthy, a feathered brow that once again is
natural but has a little bit of a
feathered little flick.
looks a bit undone.
it's always that kind of undoneness to the
makeup that we love.
it's just the right amount and it doesn't
conceal you.
it just brings out your best features.
it's not like makeup that overpowers you.
it just makes you look your best.
Sunny's face is our dream makeup line because
it was born from years and years of
makeup obsession.
it's about understanding what are our favorite formulas,
which colors are most universally flattering, what's the
cutest packaging we can put it in, and
how do we make these products as accessible
as possible?
why don't we make the perfect lip?
why don't we get everything we love and
create the best lip ever?
and so we did.
I mean that's how we came up with
our full range of the fluff matte lip
colors.
we mixed all of our favorite lipsticks that
we've had over the years, some that we
scraped from the bottom of the barrel, and
really just formulated that to create these perfect
universally flattering warm tones that really suit a
wide range of skin tones.
I mean we've tried it on so many
types and every shade remarkably looks so good
on everyone.
I think that's what's the most exciting thing
about creating these products is making products that
women feel so much excitement about and that
they gush over and that they love and
we know this because we feel the exact
same way.
that's the way that we develop the products
to create things that people get so excited
over and make them feel so good about
themselves and make them feel like this product
was really made for me.
you know and that's why Sunny Space is
really beauty that gets you because we get
you.
we are you.
we use the product and we know it
and we love it and we developed it
and we poured every bit of ourselves in
developing every single color and product and formula.
Sunny Space is everything we love about makeup
that we think you might love too.